smobookstores.com 2018-06-18

# Privacy Policy

**_Privacy Policy_**

Thank you for accessing the [www.smobookstores.com](http://www.smobookstores.com/www.smobookstores.com) Website(“Site”) operated by Syarikat Muda Osman Sdn Bhd. We respect your privacy and want to protect your personal information. Because of that, we appreciate customer’s trust and will do so carefully and sensibly of taking care of customer personal information.

This privacy policy explains how Syarikat Muda Osman Sdn Bhd uses the information collected on our website. Any queries about this statement or collected personal information can be directed to _[online@smobookstores.com](http://mudaosman.com.my/mailto:online@smobookstores.com)_ or by click here.The provision of personal information is not necessary in order to use most of this website. However, if you wish to take advantage of some specialized and/or personalized services offered under this website, you will need to provide some specific information. By visiting the site directly or through another site, you accept the practices described in this Policy.

**  
This privacy policy applies to the Site. Please see below for details.**

******_Disclaimers/Denial_**

Government of Malaysia and Syarikat Muda Osman Sdn Bhd is not responsible for any loss or damage caused by the use of information from this site.

**_Consent_**

The use of our website means that you consent to the use of your personal information as explain in this page. Changes to or modifications of our Privacy Policy will be posted on this web page. Please read carefully the Terms and Conditions of our website at [www.smobookstores.com](http://www.smobookstores.com/)

**_Information Collection and Use  _**

****We collect information from you in several different ways on this Site. One goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. For example, we can use your personal information to:

  * Help make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once. 
  * Help you quickly find information, products, and services.
  * Help us create content that is most relevant to you.
  * Alert you to new information, products, and services that we offer.
  * Verify and process your personal particulars and payments.
  * Respond to your requests and queries.

**_Information Disclosure_**

Syarikat Muda Osman Sdn Bhd may disclose to third parties certain aggregate information given by customer during registration applications. Syarikat Muda Osman Sdn. Bhd. will not disclose to any individuals the information given by customer such as name, address, email address and telephone number without customer prior consent except for the extent necessary or appropriate to comply with applicable laws or in legal proceedings.

**_Security_**

We have taken appropriate steps to protect information both online and off-line. If you have a query on the same, please feel free to contact us at [online@smobookstores.com](mailto:online@smobookstores.com) or click here.

**_Updates To This Policy_**

If we change or update this Privacy Policy, we will post changes and updates on the Site so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use and disclose. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated. If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, please contact us at [online@smobookstores.com](mailto:online@smobookstores.com) or click here.

**What you will receive from us when you subscribe SMO BOOKSTORES ONLINE e-newsletter?**

Upon subscribing to our SMO BOOKSTORES ONLINE e-newsletter, you will be receiving promotional emails from us which includes monthly promotions, new titles, in-store news and etc.  

**How to unsubscribe the e-newsletter from SMO BOOKSTORES ONLINE?**

If you wish to unsubscribe our e-newsletter, please log on to [www.smobookstores.com](http://www.smobookstores.com/) , go to Account setting and click "No" for E-Newsletter option and you will automatically be excluded from any e-newsletters from us. If you have any queries about how to unsubscribe our e-newsletter, please email us at [online@smobookstores.com](mailto:online@smobookstores.com) or contact us at 09-77335555 also by click here.  

Any email we send to you will contain an easy automated unsubscribe link so that you can opt-out of the subscription. Simply follow the indications in the email.   

**Where and how to ask questions or file complaints?**

If you have further queries, please email us at [online@smobookstores.com](mailto:online@smobookstores.com) or click here.

**SYARIKAT MUDA OSMAN SDN BHD (163785-W)**

PT 2422, Jalan 4A/44,

Kawasan Perindustrian Pengkalan Chepa II,

16100 Kota Bharu, 

Kelantan.

Tel:  +609 7733555

Fax: +609 7733444

**Operating Hours :**  9 am to 6 pm (Saturday to Thursday, except public holidays)
